http://bbmbattery.com/pages/terms-conditions

Alkaline Batteries Energizer Hearing AidSpeciality Alkaline BatteriesStandard Alkaline Batteries 9VAAAAAAAAACDWatch & Electronics BatteriesAnalyzer & Measurement EquipmentAutomatic Flusher BatteriesBaby Monitor Batteries BinatoneDeteweEvenfloFisher PriceGracoLorexMotorolaOricomPhilipsSanikSonySummer InfantBattery Chargers AA, AAA, 9V ChargersBattery / Charger KitsLi Ion & LiPoly ChargersNi-Mh & Ni-CD ChargersSLA Chargers Powersonic SLA ChargersOther SLA ChargersCamera BatteriesClock BatteriesComputer Accessory BatteriesCustom Battery PacksCustom Battery Pack DesignCustom TerminationCustom Battery QuoteDog Collar Batteries AetertekDogtraDog WatchDT SystemsGarminInnotekInvisible FenceKineticPet StopPetSafeSportDogTri-TronicsDoor & Lock BatterieseBike & Electric Scooter BatteriesEmergency Lighting Batteries All-FitApplied TechnologyAritechAriusAtliteAstra-LiteBeghelliChlorideCooper LightingCTLDantonaDay-BriteDC BatteryDual-LiteEmergi-LiteEnergizerEvenliteEvergreenExitronixGEGenlyteGloscoGS-MelcotecHubbellInterstateITIKaufelKenallLegrandLife SystemsLightAlarmsLithoniaLowesLumacellMaxPowerMinboMitsubishiMoltechNational Power Corp.OmronOSIPanasonicPowercellPowersonicPrescoliteRath MicrotechSAFTSanyoSchlumbergerSealiteSharpSimkarSimonSure-LitesT&BTEIGTeledyneTETGTOPAUnipowerUnitechWestcoFault Indicator BatteriesFlashlightsGaming System BatteriesGPS Batteries FalcomGarminHPIridiumJuniperMagellanSkyGolfSokkiaSportDogTomTomTopconHeadset Batteries AT&TBlueParrotBoseCardo SystemsChatterboxDr. DreGlobalGPJabra/GN NetcomKeelerMicrosoftMotorolaNokiaPanasonicPlantronicsRadio ShackSamsungSchuBerthSenaSennheiserSonyTV EarsUltralifeWilliams Sound3MHome & Office BatteriesIndustrial Control BatteriesIndustrial Robot Batteries ABB RoboticsOkumaYamahaYaskawa MotomanLantern BatteriesLaptop & Tablet BatteriesLithium Batteries 3.0 V - FDK/Sanyo/Varta3.6 V - SAFT9.0 V - Energizer/UltralifeElectrochemEnergizerPanasonicSpecialty Lithium BatteriesTadiranLithium Batteries- Rechargeable Lithium-IonLi-Polymer Normal Drain Li-Polymer CellsHigh Drain Li-Polymer CellsPowersonic LiFeP04Lithium Coin Cells Rechargeable Lithium Coin CellsNon-Rechargeable Lithium Coin CellsLine Recloser BatteriesMedical Equipment BatteriesMeter Batteries ElectrometerFlow MeterGas MeterMegohmmeterPower MeterPressure MeterScopemeterSignal MeterSpectrodensitometerUtility MeterWater MeterNi-CD Batteries A2/3A4/5AAA1/3AAAAAC1/2CSub C1/2 Sub C4/5 Sub CD1/2DF100mAh - 200mAh250mAh - 600mAh700mAh - 1100mAh1200mAh - 1400mAh1500mAh - 1800mAh1900mAh - 3500mAh4000mAh - 5500mAh7000mAh - 8500mAhNi-MH Batteries A2/3A4/3A4/5AAA1/3AA2/3AA4/5AAAAA1/2AAA1/3AAA2/3AAA7/5AAACSub C4/5 Sub CDF9.0VButton CellSpecialty Ni-Mh Batteries15mAh - 199mAh200mAh - 350mAh400mAh - 600mAh700mAh - 1000mAh1100mAh - 1500mAh1600mAh - 1900mAh2000mAh - 2500mAh2500mAh - 2700mAh3000mAh - 3800mAh3800mAh - 4500mAh5000mAh - 15000mAhOEM / ODM BatteriesPayment Terminal BatteriesPersonal Care BatteriesPhone Batteries AEGAastraAgfeo DectAkaiAlcatelAmericanAmeritechAppleAtivaAT&TAudiolineAudiovoxAuerswald ComfortAvantAvayaBTBang & OlufsenBellBeocommBetacomBinatoneBlueparrotBosch AtusCable & WirelessCATCidcoCiscoClarityClearoneCobraCobyConairCortelcoDeteweDoroDualphoneEasypackElmeg DectEmpireEngeniusFisherFunktelGarminGEGPGrandstreamGrundig ScenosHPHTCHuaweiIBMIridiumJacob JensenJ-TechJuniperKonftelLGLifetecLogicomLucentMaestroMedionMetropcsMemorexMidlandMitelMotorolaMuraphoneNECNTLNetlinkNokiaNomadNortelOlympiaOptexPalmPanasonicPhilipsPhone MatePolycomRadio ShackRayovacRCARTXSamsungSanikSanyoSBCSharpSiemensSokkiaSonySnomSpectralinkSprintStarpagerSwisstoneSwissvoiceT-ComTCLTelekomTelematrixTelradTelstraTiptelTMobileTopcomToshibaUnidenUnifyVergeVodafoneV TechWalkerWave TechnologiesWintonicZTEPLC / CNC Batteries ABBAllen BradleyBosch RexrothCutler HammerDeltaDensoDraegerEatonEpsonFuji ElectricGE Fanuc / FanucHaasHitachiIntelligent Actuator Inc.JEL Corp.KawasakiKitamuraKomo MachineKoyo DirectKukaLeBlondMaxellMazakMilacronMitsubishiModiconMori SeikiNachiNUMOkumaOmronPanasonicRenishawSanyoSchneider ElectricSiemensStarTelemecaniqueTestoTexas InstrumentsToshibaToyo Denki (Toyo Electric)ToyodaYamahaYaskawaYokogawaPowerSport BatteriesPower Tool BatteriesPrinter BatteriesRebuilds & RetrofitsRemote Control Batteries AbitronAcoustic ResearchCrestronDamEarmuffESPNGoProHarmanHBCHetronicI-ConIkusiKomatsuLETVLifeShieldLogitechMarantzMagnetekMonsterNevoNvidiaOne For AllPalfingerPhilipsPlaystationRTIScanrecoSonosUniversalXpendScanner Batteries BanksysBearcatCasioChameleonCornwall TechForceDatalogic / Falcon / PSCDensoFujitsuHoneywellHuskeyIcomIntermecInterstateJanamKeyenceLXEMac MentorMatcoMetrologicMotorola / SymbolNascarOmniOTCPantonePhaserPsionRadio ShackSokkiaSportcatTeklogixTrunk TrackersUnidenUnitechVidexVocollectWASPZebraSealed Lead Acid Batteries Powersonic DCG SeriesPDC SeriesPG SeriesPHR SeriesPS SeriesPSH Series2V Powersonic4V Powersonic6V Powersonic8V Powersonic12V PowersonicPanasonic 6V Panasonic12V PanasonicGenesis / Yuasa / Enersys Cyclon Genesis / Yuasa / Enersys CyclonMono Blocks2V Cylindrical CellsSecurity Alarm BatteriesSpeaker BatteriesSurvey Equipment BatteriesTwo-Way Radio BatteriesUPS Batteries AblerexAlpha-TechAPC - RBSSiemensTripp-LiteVacuum Cleaner BatteriesVoting Machine Batteries
Skip to content
Toll Free: 1-888-328 6587
Log in Sign up
Cart
(0)
Check Out
Menu Site navigation
Home
My Account
About Us
Contact Us
Blog
Shipping
Terms & Conditions
Maintaining your Privacy and Security BBM knows that you are concerned about the privacy and security of your personal information. Information such as your address is needed to purchase at bbmbattery.com. To provide you with a safe and secure shopping experience, we use the highest level of security available. Internet Explorer 6.0 or higher supports this level of security.
Who is BBM? We are the owner and operator of the bbmbattery.com website.
What does BBM use your Personal Information for? Information collected by BBM is used to: allow you to order products and services, and to participate in special promotions; verify credit card and payment information; improve the site by observing the pages and products that are most popular; and to personalize the delivery of information and recommend products and services to you.
Your personal information may also be used to create statistics that we use to measure our performance. These statistics do not contain any information that could identify you personally. BBM does not give or sell your personal information to any organization, for any purpose.
When is your Personal Information Collected? Personal information is requested when you browse bbmbattery.com as a guest and request literature and/or quotations and/or feedback. When you place an order, we request personal information about you including your credit card number, email address, shipping address, billing address and telephone number. This allows us to process your order correctly.
Who may have Access to your Personal Information? Strict controls are maintained over access to personal information that you share with bbmbattery.com. Within BBM, we strictly control access to your personal information to employees who need this information to serve you or to the employees who analyze our performance to measure and improve bbmbattery.com.
Other Organizations If you gain access to bbmbattery.com through another website or portal, any information that you shared with that website or portal prior to entering into bbmbattery.com is not controlled by bbmbattery.com. BBM will track and review statistics on the traffic directed to bbmbattery.com by other websites or portals. Your personal information will not be shared with these third party organizations unless you have given us permission to do so. At times, a third party may sponsor a contest; offer a service or promotion to bbmbattery.com visitors. We will let you know if your personal information will be shared with that third party so that you can choose whether or not you wish to participate. BBM may share statistics about the performance of bbmbattery.com with other reputable organizations. These include statistics such as the total number of website users. Your personal information cannot be identified from these statistics.
Would BBM disclose your Personal Information to anyone else? By law, BBM must comply with the law and co-operate with law enforcement and other officials in any investigation requiring either personal or account information, including any information provided online through bbmbattery.com.
Does BBM use “Cookies”? Your web browser places cookie files on your computer’s hard drive, and bbmbattery.com uses cookies to remember information that you gave to us so you don’t have to re-enter it each time that you visit bbmbattery.com. Cookies also help us to understand which areas are popular by showing us how shoppers use bbmbattery.com. This allows us to continually improve bbmbattery.com.
Your Personal Information is Secure. BBM believes that securing your personal information is a very important part of our job. That means that your credit card information and personal information is always secure with us. For instance, when you visit bbmbattery.com and provide personal information or place an order, it’s done through a secure server that encrypts all information that you provide before sending it to bbmbattery.com. Only when it reaches bbmbattery.com is your information decrypted.
Getting your Consent. By using bbmbattery.com, you are consenting to the collection and use of personal information and account information by BBM for the purposes set out in this policy.
Payments by Credit CardWe do accept Visa / Master Card / AMEX / Paypal on our website.
Changes to this Privacy Policy All changes will be posted on bbmbattery.com promptly to inform visitors of what information is collected, how it is used, and under what circumstances it may be disclosed.
Do you have any Questions or Comments? BBM welcomes your feedback regarding bbmbattery.com and/or this policy. If you have any comments or suggestions, please contact us by email at john@bbmbattery.com
